Marvelous Designer Linux Enterprise Edition will be released on September 30th.
Marvelous Designer Linux Edition will provide support for RockyLinux9 and higher versions,
as well as compatible with Red Hat Enterprise Linux9 and subsequent versions.
The new version is designed to ensure super-stable and precise simulation,
which provides you with a smooth operating experience,
and easily integrates into various 3D work processes.
In addition, the version also provides a Python API,
allowing you to write and run scripts directly within Marvelous Designer,
import and export files, adjust and control simulation settings and other parameters,
as well as more automation operations.
Want to experience the Linux version of Marvelous Designer?
Visit our official website or contact sales at marvellousdesigner.com to get a free trial.